<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="lib/rfc2629.xslt" ?>
<!-- generated by https://github.com/cabo/kramdown-rfc2629 version 1.0.20 -->
<!DOCTYPE rfc SYSTEM "lib/rfc2629.dtd">
<rfc ipr="trust200902" category="info">
  <?rfc toc="yes"?>
  <?rfc tocindent="yes"?>
  <?rfc sortrefs="yes"?>
  <?rfc symrefs="yes"?>
  <?rfc strict="yes"?>
  <?rfc compact="yes"?>
  <?rfc comments="yes"?>
  <?rfc inline="yes"?>
  <front>
    <title>Delta Encoding</title>
    <author initials="B." surname="Smith" fullname="Bob Smith">
      <organization>Google</organization>
      <address>
        <email>bob@google.com</email>
        <uri>https://www.google.com/</uri>
      </address>
    </author>
    <date year="2014"/>
    <area>General</area>
    <keyword>Internet-Draft</keyword>
    <abstract>
      <t>Delta encoding mechanism to reduce the payload size by only transferring the diff.</t>
    </abstract>
  </front>
  <middle>
    <section anchor="introduction" title="Introduction">
      <t>Intro goes here.</t>
      <section anchor="notational-conventions" title="Notational Conventions">
        <t>The key words “MUST”, “MUST NOT”, “REQUIRED”, “SHALL”, “SHALL NOT”, “SHOULD”, “SHOULD NOT”, “RECOMMENDED”, “MAY”, and “OPTIONAL” in this document are to be interpreted as described in <xref target="RFC2119"/>.</t>
        <t>This document uses the Augmented Backus-Naur Form (ABNF) notation of <xref target="RFC5234"/> with the list rule extension defined in <xref target="RFC7230"/>, Appendix B. It includes by reference the DIGIT rule from <xref target="RFC5234"/>; the OWS, field-name and quoted-string rules from <xref target="RFC7230"/>; and the parameter rule from <xref target="RFC7231"/>.</t>
      </section>
    </section>
    <section anchor="iana-considerations" title="IANA Considerations">
      <t>This document defines the “A”, “B”, “C”, and “D” HTTP request fields and registers them in the Permanent Message Header Fields registry.</t>
      <t>
        <list style="symbols">
          <t>Header field name: A</t>
          <t>Applicable protocol: HTTP</t>
          <t>Status: standard</t>
          <t>Author/Change controller: Bob Smith, bob@google.com</t>
          <t>Specification document(s): [this document]</t>
          <t>Related information: for Delta Encoding</t>
        </list>
      </t>
    </section>
    <section anchor="security-considerations" title="Security Considerations">
      <t>Text goes here.</t>
    </section>
  </middle>
  <back>
    <references title="Normative References">
      <reference anchor="RFC2119">
        <front>
          <title abbrev="RFC Key Words">Key words for use in RFCs to Indicate Requirement Levels</title>
          <author initials="S." surname="Bradner" fullname="Scott Bradner">
            <organization>Harvard University</organization>
            <address>
              <postal>
                <street>1350 Mass. Ave.</street>
                <street>Cambridge</street>
                <street>MA 02138</street>
              </postal>
              <phone>- +1 617 495 3864</phone>
              <email>sob@harvard.edu</email>
            </address>
          </author>
          <date year="1997" month="March"/>
          <area>General</area>
          <keyword>keyword</keyword>
          <abstract>
            <t>
   In many standards track documents several words are used to signify
   the requirements in the specification.  These words are often
   capitalized.  This document defines these words as they should be
   interpreted in IETF documents.  Authors who follow these guidelines
   should incorporate this phrase near the beginning of their document:

<list><t>
      The key words "MUST", "MUST NOT", "REQUIRED", "SHALL", "SHALL
      NOT", "SHOULD", "SHOULD NOT", "RECOMMENDED",  "MAY", and
      "OPTIONAL" in this document are to be interpreted as described in
      RFC 2119.
</t></list></t>
            <t>
   Note that the force of these words is modified by the requirement
   level of the document in which they are used.
</t>
          </abstract>
        </front>
        <seriesInfo name="BCP" value="14"/>
        <seriesInfo name="RFC" value="2119"/>
        <format type="TXT" octets="4723" target="http://www.rfc-editor.org/rfc/rfc2119.txt"/>
        <format type="HTML" octets="17970" target="http://xml.resource.org/public/rfc/html/rfc2119.html"/>
        <format type="XML" octets="5777" target="http://xml.resource.org/public/rfc/xml/rfc2119.xml"/>
      </reference>
      <reference anchor="RFC5234">
        <front>
          <title>Augmented BNF for Syntax Specifications: ABNF</title>
          <author initials="D." surname="Crocker" fullname="D. Crocker">
            <organization/>
          </author>
          <author initials="P." surname="Overell" fullname="P. Overell">
            <organization/>
          </author>
          <date year="2008" month="January"/>
          <abstract>
            <t>Internet technical specifications often need to define a formal syntax.  Over the years, a modified version of Backus-Naur Form (BNF), called Augmented BNF (ABNF), has been popular among many Internet specifications.  The current specification documents ABNF.  It balances compactness and simplicity with reasonable representational power.  The differences between standard BNF and ABNF involve naming rules, repetition, alternatives, order-independence, and value ranges.  This specification also supplies additional rule definitions and encoding for a core lexical analyzer of the type common to several Internet specifications. [STANDARDS-TRACK]</t>
          </abstract>
        </front>
        <seriesInfo name="STD" value="68"/>
        <seriesInfo name="RFC" value="5234"/>
        <format type="TXT" octets="26359" target="http://www.rfc-editor.org/rfc/rfc5234.txt"/>
      </reference>
      <reference anchor="RFC5226">
        <front>
          <title>Guidelines for Writing an IANA Considerations Section in RFCs</title>
          <author initials="T." surname="Narten" fullname="T. Narten">
            <organization/>
          </author>
          <author initials="H." surname="Alvestrand" fullname="H. Alvestrand">
            <organization/>
          </author>
          <date year="2008" month="May"/>
          <abstract>
            <t>Many protocols make use of identifiers consisting of constants and other well-known values. Even after a protocol has been defined and deployment has begun, new values may need to be assigned (e.g., for a new option type in DHCP, or a new encryption or authentication transform for IPsec). To ensure that such quantities have consistent values and interpretations across all implementations, their assignment must be administered by a central authority. For IETF protocols, that role is provided by the Internet Assigned Numbers Authority (IANA).&lt;/t&gt;&lt;t&gt; In order for IANA to manage a given namespace prudently, it needs guidelines describing the conditions under which new values can be assigned or when modifications to existing values can be made. If IANA is expected to play a role in the management of a namespace, IANA must be given clear and concise instructions describing that role. This document discusses issues that should be considered in formulating a policy for assigning values to a namespace and provides guidelines for authors on the specific text that must be included in documents that place demands on IANA.&lt;/t&gt;&lt;t&gt; This document obsoletes RFC 2434. This document specifies an Internet Best Current Practices for the Internet Community, and requests discussion and suggestions for improvements.</t>
          </abstract>
        </front>
        <seriesInfo name="BCP" value="26"/>
        <seriesInfo name="RFC" value="5226"/>
        <format type="TXT" octets="66160" target="http://www.rfc-editor.org/rfc/rfc5226.txt"/>
      </reference>
      <reference anchor="RFC7230">
        <front>
          <title>Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP/1.1): Message Syntax and Routing</title>
          <author initials="R." surname="Fielding" fullname="R. Fielding">
            <organization/>
          </author>
          <author initials="J." surname="Reschke" fullname="J. Reschke">
            <organization/>
          </author>
          <date year="2014" month="June"/>
          <abstract>
            <t>The Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) is a stateless application-level protocol for distributed, collaborative, hypertext information systems.  This document provides an overview of HTTP architecture and its associated terminology, defines the "http" and "https" Uniform Resource Identifier (URI) schemes, defines the HTTP/1.1 message syntax and parsing requirements, and describes related security concerns for implementations.</t>
          </abstract>
        </front>
        <seriesInfo name="RFC" value="7230"/>
        <format type="TXT" octets="205947" target="http://www.rfc-editor.org/rfc/rfc7230.txt"/>
      </reference>
      <reference anchor="RFC7231">
        <front>
          <title>Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP/1.1): Semantics and Content</title>
          <author initials="R." surname="Fielding" fullname="R. Fielding">
            <organization/>
          </author>
          <author initials="J." surname="Reschke" fullname="J. Reschke">
            <organization/>
          </author>
          <date year="2014" month="June"/>
          <abstract>
            <t>The Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) is a stateless \%application- level protocol for distributed, collaborative, hypertext information systems.  This document defines the semantics of HTTP/1.1 messages, as expressed by request methods, request header fields, response status codes, and response header fields, along with the payload of messages (metadata and body content) and mechanisms for content negotiation.</t>
          </abstract>
        </front>
        <seriesInfo name="RFC" value="7231"/>
        <format type="TXT" octets="235053" target="http://www.rfc-editor.org/rfc/rfc7231.txt"/>
      </reference>
    </references>
  </back>
</rfc>
